A Guide to the Laurance S. Rockefeller papers, Mary French Rockefeller papers FA1731
Rockefeller Archive Center
Laurance S. Rockefeller papers, Mary French Rockefeller papers
1918-1997
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller, Mary French (1910-1997)
Rockefeller, Laurance Spelman (1910-2004)
FA1731
50 Cubic Feet 123 letter document boxes and 7 legal document boxes.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select material restricted as noted, in accordance with the terms of donation from the Laurance S. Rockefeller estate. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Arrangement
The Mary French Rockefeller papers are arranged in original order, as received in the following series:
Series 1: Women's Interests, and Civic, Educational, and Religious Interests Series 2: Personal papers and Family Interests Series 3: Art and Culture
Scope and Contents
Mary French Rockefeller, philanthropist and wife of Laurance S. Rockefeller, spent her career promoting and advocating for leadership opportunities for women and girls. This collection of her papers documents her activities in civic, educational and religious organizations as well as her interests in culture and the ar
The collection primarily documents her decades of service to the Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) and dedicated advocacy for women and girls throughout the world. Mary began her service to YWCA as a member of the national board in 1951, and became vice-chair of the International Division in 1955, continuing as either vice-chair or chair through 1973. In the late 1950s and early 1960s, she also served as chair of the YWCA's World Service Council, and was then elected to the Board of Trustees in 1988.
Mary French Rockefeller also hosted and/or planned and participated in many events and fundraising and development campaigns, as well as traveled extensively, often with Laurance S. Rockefeller, to study YWCA activities and programs, and promote the growth and development of women leaders, throughout the world
The collection also documents Mary French Rockefeller's activities as a committee member or trustee of the Foreign Policy Association, Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary, New York Community Trust, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, Spelman College, United Board for Christian Education in Asia, and the Whitney Museum of American Art.
Mary French Rockefeller's personal giving, and a selection of files from her giving program, are documented as well as a variety of Rockefeller family activities and events.
- Women's Interests, and Civic, Educational, and Religious Interests, 1932-1997; 1; 42.41 Cubic Feet 103 letter document boxes and 7 legal document boxes.
  - YWCA - Building Fund - Gifts to International Building Fund, 1969-1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - YWCA - International Building Fund, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - YWCA - International Building Fund - Lebanon, 1961-1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - YWCA - International Building Fund, 1971-1987 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - YWCA - International Building Fund - Projects, 1968-1994 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - YWCA - International Building Fund - Projects - Amman, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - YWCA - International Building Fund - Projects - South America, 1967-1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - YWCA - International Division Committee - Set Up, 1961-1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - YWCA - International Building Fund - Correspondence, 1967-1990 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - YWCA - International Division Receptions - Leila Anderson Luncheon, 1980 November 14 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - YWCA - International Division Receptions - Leila Anderson Tea, 1973 May 9 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - YWCA - International Division Receptions - International Consultation Dinner, 834 Fifth Avenue, 1974 October 28 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - YWCA - International Division Receptions - Luncheon for the Honorable Isabel Catto, 1971 February 17 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - YWCA - International Division Receptions - Oakes-Woodward Tea, 1972 December 13 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - YWCA - International Division Receptions - YWCA Reception, San Diego, 1973 March 26 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - YWCA - International Division Receptions - Elizabeth Palmer Tea, 834 Fifth Avenue, 1972 October 18 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - YWCA - International Division Receptions - Luncheon for Mrs. Athens Tsouderos-Athanassiou, 834 Fifth Avenue, 1970 April 3 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - YWCA - International Division Receptions - Princess Mahazent Hapte Mariam Luncheon, 1969 April 23 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - YWCA - International Division - Correspondence, 1965-1989 (Box 2, Folder 11-12)
  - YWCA - International Division - Projects - Buenos Aires, Argentina (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - YWCA - International Division - Projects - Hawaii, 1967-1973 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - YWCA - International Division - Projects - Japan, 1981 December (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - YWCA - International Division - Projects - Nutrition Project - AID, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - YWCA - International Division - Projects - Lima, Peru, 1966-1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - YWCA - International Division - Projects - St. Croix, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - YWCA - International Division - Projects - Zaire, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - YWCA - International Division - Projects - School of Social Work, Athens, Greece, 1968-1971 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - YWCA - International Study Program, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - YWCA - International Study Tour - Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - YWCA - International Consultation - General Correspondence, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - YWCA - Projects and Grants - YWCA Executive Committee - World Relations Committee, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - YWCA - Projects and Grants, 1965-1991 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - YWCA - International Voluntary Service, 1964-1970 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - YWCA - Istanbul Liaison Committee (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - YWCA - Memorial Window, National Cathedral, 1970-1977 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - YWCA - Minutes - International Division and World Relations Committees, 1964-1977 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - World YWCA - Mutual Service, 1959-1967 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - YWCA - Visitors' Service Committee, 1964-1972 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - YWCA - World Fellowship Education Committee, 1965-1968 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - YWCA - World Council Meetings, 1959-1991 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - World YWCA - Endowment Fund, 1970-1979 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - YWCA - World Service Council - General, 1970-1990 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - YWCA - World Service Council - General, 1970-1989 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - YWCA - Pension Study, 1970-1974 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - YWCA - XF Staff, 1965-1989 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Conservation, 1966-1970 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary - General, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary - General, 1988-1994 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary - Development Campaign, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary - Correspondence, 1977-1994 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary - Executive Committee, 1976-1992 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary - Nominating Committee, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Administrative Board, 1980-1992 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Correspondence, 1978-1994 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - YWCA - National Board - Trustees, 1967-1994 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - YWCA - National Board - Correspondence, 1975-1993 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - United Nations Association Advisory Council, 1977-1981 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - United Board for Christian Education in Asia, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - New York Community Trust, 1969-1994 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - YMCA-YWCA Cooperation, 1943-1979 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - YMCA-YWCA - Joint Camping Services, 1972-1991 (Box 9, Folder 1-3)
  - YWCA New York City - World Mutual Service, 1975-1991 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - YWCA New York City - General, 1972-1993 (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
  - YWCA New York City - Nominating Committee, 1985-1988 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - YWCA New York City - Day Care, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - YWCA New York City - Remarks by Mary French Rockefeller (MFR), 1970-1974 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - New York Community Trust - Distribution Committee, 1990-1994 (Box 15, Folder 3-4)
  - New York Community Trust - Distribution Committee, 1995-1997 (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
    Scope and Contents
    Board of Directors
  - New York Community Trust - MFR - Publicity and Publications, 1987-1997 (Box 12, Folder 3-5, Box 13, Folder 1-2)
  - New York Community Trust - MFR - Publicity and Publications, 1992-1993 (Box 16, Folder 1-2)
  - YWCA - International Leadership Exchange and Development (ILEAD), 1987-1989 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - New York Blood Center, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - YWCA - Fund for the Future, 1982-1986 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - UNICEF, 1995-1996 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Conference on Science and Religion, Arden House, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - YWCA - Phoenix Trip, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Christian Ministries (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Publications and Reports Received (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - James Foundation, St. James Cemetery Corporation - Board of Directors Meeting, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Union Church of Pocantico Hills - Search Committee, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted - Executive Search - Open in 2031
  - World Mercy Fund, 1980-1989 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1991-1997 (Box 16, Folder 5-6, Box 17, Folder 1-5)
  - Spelman College - General, 1972-1981 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Spelman College - Dorothy Shepard Manley Fellowship, 1965-1990 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Spelman College - Luncheon, 1961 November 15 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Spelman College - "A Legacy Continues: The Manley Years at Spelman College", 1953-1976 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    By Albert E. Manley. Published 1995.
  - Spelman College - Board of Trustees Retreat, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Spelman College - Publications and Printed Material, 1985-1991 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Woodstock Foundation - Annual Meeting, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - UNICEF - The Future United Nations Convention on the Rights of the Child, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Trinity Forum, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - "Center in the Margins - The Development of Women's Studies in a Thai University", 1995 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    PhD dissertation by Shirley Jean Miske, Michigan State University.
  - American Festival of Evangelism, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - World YWCA - General, 1970s-1990s (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
  - World YWCA - Publications, 1960s-1980s (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - World YWCA - World Council Meetings, 1975; 1987 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - YWCA - World Service Council - General, 1965-1968 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - YWCA - World Service Council - General, 1969-1986 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - YWCA - World Service Council - Individual Gifts, 1959-1964 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - YWCA - National Board, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - YWCA - National Board - International Study Program, 1980s (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - YWCA New York City - World Mutual Service, 1976-1992 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - YWCA New York (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - YWCA - Millennium 2000 Campaign, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - YWCA - MFR, 1992-1995 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - YWCA - Centennial, 1969-1992 (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
  - YWCA - World Service Council - Correspondence, 1979-1992 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - YWCA - Publications and Printed Material, 1970s-1990s (Box 23, Folder 4-5)
  - YWCA - Centennial Committee Dinner, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - YWCA - Capital Campaign, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - YWCA - Millennium 2000 Campaign, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - YWCA Camping Services - General, 1978-1997 (Box 24, Folder 4-5)
  - YWCA - National Board - Centennial Speech Material, 1953-1957 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - YWCA - Archives, 1975-1977 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - YWCA - National Board - Site Selection Committee, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - YWCA - Sadat Reception, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - YWCA - Pocantico Tour - Thank You Letters, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - YWCA - Printed Materials and Events, 1950s-1980s (Box 25, Folder 2-4)
  - YWCA - World Service Council - History, 1920-1946 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - YWCA - World Service Council, 1969-1994 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - YWCA - Capital Campaign, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - YWCA - Salem, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - YWCA - World Service Council, 1975-1996 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - YWCA - City of New York Campaign, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - YWCA - National Convention, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - YWCA - Various Board Meetings, 1991-1993 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - YWCA - General, 1969-1994 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - YWCA - International Building Fund Meetings, 1989-1990 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - YWCA - 135th Anniversary, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - YWCA - Investment Committee Meeting, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - YWCA - National Advancement Council, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - YWCA - National Initiatives, 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - YWCA - Library and Archives Project, 1995-1997 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - YWCA - 135th Anniversary - Photo Exhibit Booklets, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - YWCA - Capital Campaign, 1989-1993 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - YWCA - Convocation for Racial Justice, 1972-1973 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - YWCA - Week without Violence - Organizer's Kit, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - YWCA - Contributions, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - YWCA - Publications and Printed Material, 1973-1996 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - YWCA - Miscellaneous Meetings, 1990-1996 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - YWCA of Greater New York - Stewardship Report, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - YWCA - 30th National Convention, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - YWCA - Vice President Bush Reception, Chicago, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - YWCA - Camping Services - Planning, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Mary French Rockefeller Journal, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - YWCA - United Nations Reception, 1976 June 6 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - YWCA - Puerto Rico, 1959-1969 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - YWCA - International Division, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - YWCA - World Relations Committee Meeting, 1972 April 18 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - YWCA - Korea, 1957-1969 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - YWCA - Korea II - Park, Allen, 1958-1968 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - YWCA - Korea - Jeep, 1962-1973 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - YWCA - Anniversary Committee - Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - YWCA - National Board - Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - YWCA - National Board - "Tribute to Women in International Industry", 1979 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - YWCA - National Board - Tribute to Women in International Industry (Twin IV), Minneapolis, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - YWCA - National Board - Study Group - International Study, 1965-1968 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - YWCA - United Nations - Cooperating Organizations, 1965-1968 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - YWCA - National Board - International Dinner, 1970-1971 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - YWCA - National Board - Executive Management Convention, 1976 June (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - YWCA - National Board - International Division - Executive Committee, 1964-1976 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - YWCA New York City - Development Committee, 1972-1978 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - YWCA - Alaska, 1966-1967 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - YWCA - Japan, 1955-1963 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - YWCA - Vietnam, 1955-1967 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - YWCA - Mexico, 1968-1970 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - YWCA - Korea, 1957-1958 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - YWCA - National Board - Tribute to Women in International Industry, TWIN III, Houston, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - YWCA - National Board - Tea, Rhodesia, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - YWCA - Convention, San Diego, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - YWCA - Dorothy Height Tribute Dinner, 1986 November 5 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - YWCA - International Study Tour, 1966-1967 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Spelman College - Spelman Messenger, 1981 Winter (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - YWCA New York City - Long Range Planning, 1971-1972 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - YWCA - International Division, 1964-1973 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - YWCA - International Training Institute, 1964-1965 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - YWCA - International Training Institute - Leadership Training Project, 1952-1964 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - YWCA - International Training Institute - Fundraising, 1964-1965 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - YWCA - International Training Institute - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - YWCA - International Training Project - Fundraising - General, 1968-1969 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - YWCA - International Training Project - Latin America, 1960-1969 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - YWCA - International Study Program - Asian Focus, 1977-1979 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - YWCA - Convocation, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - YWCA New York City - Special Events, 1970-1975 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - YWCA New York City - Centennial, 1965-1970 (Box 34, Folder 3-4)
  - YWCA New York City - Centennial, 1959-1971 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - YWCA - 28th National Convention, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - YWCA - Public Information Department, 1960s-1970s (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Seminary and School Publications (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - YWCA - Sports Center, Camp Greenkill Proposal, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Mary French Rockefeller - Journal, 1951-1966 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Mary French Rockefeller - Journal, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Mary French Rockefeller - Journal, 1968-1975 (Box 39, Folder 4-5)
  - Mary French Rockefeller - Journal, 1966-1979 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary, 1982-1990 (Box 40, Folder 2-3)
  - New York Community Trust - Arts in Education, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 2-3)
  - Foreign Policy Association, 1970-1987 (Box 41, Folder 1-2)
  - YWCA - Working Papers, 1965-1974 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - YWCA - Working Papers, 1970-1990 (Box 41, Folder 4-5)
  - New York Community Trust (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - USO - Lunch, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - China Institute - Dinner, 1988 October 26 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Dissertation by Henry Charles Link, Yale University, 1916 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Brookdale Center on Aging, Hunter College, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Foreign Policy Association, 1983-1984 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary, 1967-1987 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - YWCA, 1960s-1970s (Box 43, Folder 3-4)
  - YWCA - Convention, Houston, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - YWCA - Mother's Center, 1980s (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - YWCA - World '87 Council Meeting, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - The YWCA Magazine, 1953-1968 (Box 44, Folder 3-5)
  - The YWCA Magazine, 1968-1973 (Box 45, Folder 1-5)
  - YWCA - Publications, 1980s (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - YWCA - 29th National Convention, 1982 June 3-7 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - YWCA - Guidelines for the Membership Chair and the Membership Committee, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - New York Community Trust, 1970-1986 (Box 46, Folder 8, Box 47, Folder 1-4, Box 48, Folder 1-2)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary - Board of Directors Meetings, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 1-2)
  - New York Community Trust, 1980s (Box 49, Folder 3-4)
  - YWCA - Reports, 1970s-1980s (Box 49, Folder 5, Box 50, Folder 1)
  - World YWCA Council Meeting, Ghana, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Committee on the United Nations Reception - Tribute to Women in International Industry - Notes (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - New York Community Trust - Dinners, 1984-1991 (Box 50, Folder 4-5)
  - New York Community Trust, 1985-1989 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - New York Community Trust - AIDS in New York City - Report to the Mayor, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - YWCA Center - A Proposal (YWCA-YMCA East Side Complex), 1973 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - YWCA - Phoenix Trip, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary - Darrell Green, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 1A)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary - Trip to Boston, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary - Board Meetings, 1991-1992 (Box 51, Folder 7, Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary - Board Meetings, 1993-1995 (Box 53, Folder 1-4, Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary - Board Meetings, 1996 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary - Trustees, 1992-1996 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary - Robert Cooley, 1992-1994 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary - Memos, 1979-1981 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary - Publications, 1980s-1990s (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary - Memos, 1977 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary - Memos and Meetings, 1982-1984 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary - Memos and Meetings, 1985-1986 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary - Memos and Meetings, 1987-1988 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary - Memos and Meetings, 1984-1988 (Box 55, Folder 6, Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary - Memos and Meetings, 1989 (Box 56, Folder 2-4)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary - Memos and Meetings, 1990 (Box 56, Folder 5, Box 57, Folder 1-2)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary - Memos and Meetings, 1991-1993 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary - Memos and Meetings, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 4-5)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary - Memos and Meetings, 1995 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary - Memos and Meetings, 1996-1997 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - YWCA - Fund for the Future - Mary French Rockefeller Correspondence and Publicationss, 1984-1987 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - YWCA - Fund for the Future - Correspondence, 1982-1986 (Box 58, Folder 4-5)
  - YWCA - Fund for the Future, 1982-1986 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - YWCA - Fund for the Future - Corporate Support, 1982-1985 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - YWCA - Fund for the Future - Corporate Committee, 1983-1985 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - YWCA - Fund for the Future - Evaluation Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - YWCA - Fund for the Future - Executive Committee, 1983-1985 (Box 59, Folder 5, Box 60, Folder 1)
  - YWCA - Fund for the Future - General, 1983-1986 (Box 60, Folder 2-5)
  - International Center of the Disabled - Annual Report 1985, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Central Park Conservancy, 1988-1992 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Foundation for Child Development - Annual Meeting, 1992 September 24 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - YWCA - National Board - General, 1958-1963 (Box 62, Folder 1-2)
  - YWCA - National Board - Correspondence, 1965-1972 (Box 62, Folder 3-5)
  - YWCA - Leaders - "Great Women" Book, 1962-1973 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Greenwich YWCA, 1966-1969 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - YWCA - Advisory Council - National Support, 1958-1968 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - YWCA - International Division - Correspondence, 1958-1968 (Box 63, Folder 4-5)
  - YWCA - International Division - General, 1965-1973 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - YWCA - International Division - Long Range Planning Committee, 1961-1963 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - YWCA - Invitations to Speak (MFR) - Accepts, 1963-1969 (Box 64, Folder 2-3)
  - YWCA - Invitations to Speak (MFR) - Regrets, 1966-1976 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - The James Madison Council, Library of Congress - LSR, 1992 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - National Geographic Article - Latin America, 1967 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - National Geographic Article - South America, 1964-1974 (Box 65, Folder 1-2)
  - National Geographic Article, 1962-1967 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - National Geographic - South Pacific, 1972-1979 (Box 65, Folder 4, Box 66, Folder 1)
  - YWCA - Round the World Trip 1, 1962 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - YWCA - Round the World Trip 2, 1963 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - YWCA New York City, 1965-1969 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - YWCA - World Service Council, 1959-1968 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - YWCA - World's Fair Committee - Reception, 1964 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - YWCA - National Board - Speech Material, 1960-1988 (Box 67, Folder 1-5)
  - Bobst Foundation, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Brick Church - Tea, 1958-1961 (Box 68, Folder 4)